toponavi.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and use personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which the information is collected. 
  * We will collect and use personal information only in order to fulfill these objectives, specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary to fulfill these goals. 
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual. 
  * Personal data should be consistent with the purposes for which it will be used, and, as necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete and current. 
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * We will make available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

We use Google Analytics to analyze how the product is used. These data enable us to optimize the product and its functions. We use it in an anonymous form. 

We use third-party advertising on toponavi.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons (for example, Google using Google AdSense). It is usually used for the purpose of geo-targeting or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
